[
    {"question": "black sheep", "answer": "（家族内での）厄介者、恥"},
    {"question": "take sth as gospel", "answer": "（疑わないで）〜を信じる"},
    {"question": "roll sth out", "answer": "〜を新発売する、新しく開始する"},
    {"question": "rough sb up", "answer": "〜を打ち負かす；暴力を振るう"},
    {"question": "the long and short of it", "answer": "まとめ"},
    {"question": "not an exact science", "answer": "必ず成功するわけじゃない"},
    {"question": "on second thought", "answer": "やっぱり"},
    {"question": "more art than science", "answer": "完璧に行うのは）現実的に難しい"},
    {"question": "bite ones's (own) tongue", "answer": "思ったことを言わないようにする"},
    {"question": "under lock and key", "answer": "厳重に保管した"},
    {"question": "rough around the edges", "answer": "完成度が低い、洗練されていない"},
    {"question": "at the eleventh hour", "answer": "土壇場で、ぎりぎりで"},
    {"question": "over the hill", "answer": "もう歳の、全盛期を過ぎた"},
    {"question": "settle one's differences", "answer": "仲直りする、和解する"},
    {"question": "put in the hard yards", "answer": "最大限努力する"},
    {"question": "time-sensitive", "answer": "時間的制限のある、締切がある"},
    {"question": "have an eye on for identifying sth", "answer": "〜を見つける目がある"},
    {"question": "play out of one's skin", "answer": "最高のパフォーマンスをみせる"},
    {"question": "throw in the towel", "answer": "あきめる"},
    {"question": "diamond in the rough", "answer": "素質がある人"},

    {"question": "take the sting out of sth", "answer": "～の影響を和らげる"},
    {"question": "shoot for the stars", "answer": "高いレベルを目指す；高望みをする"},
    {"question": "at the end of one's rope", "answer": "（我慢などの）限界である"},
    {"question": "keep sth to oneself", "answer": "～を人に言わないようにする"},
    {"question": "weigh on sb's mind", "answer": "～の気を重くする"},
    {"question": "table sth", "answer": "～を持ち越す；議題に乗せる"},
    {"question": "straight and narrow", "answer": "正しい道、正しい行為"},
    {"question": "pizzazz", "answer": "活気、華麗さ"},
    {"question": "strike while the iron's hot", "answer": "出来るときにやる"},
    {"question": "talk shop", "answer": "仕事の話をする"},
    {"question": "right under sb's nose", "answer": "～のすぐそこに、目先に"},
    {"question": "go Dutch", "answer": "割り勘にする"},
    {"question": "long shot", "answer": "成功の見込みが少ないこと"},
    {"question": "the powers that be", "answer": "上層部、（政府などの）権力者"},
    {"question": "keep sb up at night", "answer": "～を心配させる"},
    {"question": "like two peas in a pod", "answer": "瓜二つな、とても似ている"},
    {"question": "razor-thin", "answer": "ものすごく小さい"},
    {"question": "punchy", "answer": "（話やスピーチ）力強い"},
    {"question": "lax", "answer": "ゆるい、怠けた"},
    {"question": "show face", "answer": "顔を出す"},

    {"question": "firing on all cylinders", "answer": "調子がピークの、フル稼働している"},
    {"question": "ignorance is bliss", "answer": "知らないほうがいいこともある"},
    {"question": "steady the ship", "answer": "（状況を）落ち着かせる"},
    {"question": "collecting dust", "answer": "放置している、ずっと使っていない"},
    {"question": "be of two minds", "answer": "優柔不断である"},
    {"question": "gas-guzzler", "answer": "燃費の悪い車"},
    {"question": "so on and so forth", "answer": "などなど"},
    {"question": "bread and butter", "answer": "最も基本的なもの；本業"},
    {"question": "straw that broke the camel's back", "answer": "我慢の限界を超えさせること"},
    {"question": "nag (sb)", "answer": "~にがみがみ言う"},
    {"question": "married to the idea", "answer": "その考えに固執した"},
    {"question": "make or break sth/sb", "answer": "～の運命を分ける"},
    {"question": "trailblazer", "answer": "革新に挑戦する人、先駆者"},
    {"question": "take sth as read", "answer": "各自～を既に読んでいると考える"},
    {"question": "soften the blow", "answer": "ショックを和らげる"},
    {"question": "put one's money where one's mouth is", "answer": "有言実行する"},
    {"question": "shell-shocked", "answer": "ビクビクして、ショックを受けて"},
    {"question": "hindsight is 20/20", "answer": "後からいうのは簡単だ"},
    {"question": "show sb the ropes", "answer": "～にやり方を教える、コツを教える"},
    {"question": "put two and two together", "answer": "（既知の事実を基に）推測する"},

    {"question": "red herring", "answer": "論点のすり替え、目くらまし"},
    {"question": "take stock of sth", "answer": "～を評価する、調査する"},
    {"question": "pull some strings", "answer": "コネを利用する；陰で物事を操る"},
    {"question": "snappy", "answer": "短気な、イライラした"},
    {"question": "call the shots", "answer": "決める権利を持つ"},
    {"question": "be-all and end-all", "answer": "最も重要なこと"},
    {"question": "a few sandwiches short of a picnic", "answer": "ばかな"},
    {"question": "on cloud nine", "answer": "死ぬほど幸せな"},
    {"question": "once-in-a-lifetime", "answer": "一生に一度の"},
    {"question": "ask for the world", "answer": "無理なお願いをする"},
    {"question": "under the table", "answer": "不正な方法で、こっそり"},
    {"question": "smooth things over", "answer": "丸く収める；諸問題を解決する"},
    {"question": "David and Goliath", "answer": "どちらが勝つか明らかな"},
    {"question": "sight for sore eyes", "answer": "目の保養"},
    {"question": "tempest in a teapot", "answer": "大したことのない騒ぎ、問題"},
    {"question": "sick", "answer": "最高な、カッコいい"},
    {"question": "all's well that ends well", "answer": "終わりよければ全て良し"},
    {"question": "selective memory", "answer": "都合よく覚えていること"},
    {"question": "sell oneself shortt", "answer": "自分を安売りする、過小評価する"},
    {"question": "be in for the long haul", "answer": "長期的にやるつもりがある"},

    {"question": "speaks for itself", "answer": "説明不要である"},
    {"question": "pump iron", "answer": "ウェイトトレーニングをする"},
    {"question": "move heaven and earth", "answer": "何でもする、全力を尽くす"},
    {"question": "throw sb a bone", "answer": "～をなだめる、ましにする"},
    {"question": "full steam ahead", "answer": "全力で進めて"},
    {"question": "picture this", "answer": "想像してみて"},
    {"question": "ship-shape", "answer": "完璧に整理された、きれいな"},
    {"question": "run riot", "answer": "（攻撃的に）騒ぎまわる；はびこる"},
    {"question": "kudos", "answer": "感謝、拍手、やるじゃん"},
    {"question": "stars are aligned", "answer": "好条件がそろっている"},
    {"question": "carry a tune", "answer": "うまく歌う、音を外さずに歌う"},
    {"question": "the Midas touch", "answer": "金儲けの才能"},
    {"question": "nothing to sneeze at", "answer": "ばかにならないこと、中々のもの"},
    {"question": "walk on eggshells", "answer": "言動に注意する、慎重になる"},
    {"question": "walk on sunshine", "answer": "とても上機嫌である、ハッピーである"},
    {"question": "play on words", "answer": "言葉遊び、ダジャレ"},
    {"question": "scratch the surface", "answer": "表面的なことを学ぶ、少しかじる"},
    {"question": "staycation", "answer": "休暇を自宅（周辺）で過ごす"},
    {"question": "stretch goal/target", "answer": "達成が難しい目標、高めの目標"},
    {"question": "on the way out", "answer": "（技術が）古い；退職が近い"}
]